

Contact Me

- Syria-Aleppo
- © (+963-943581149 (+963-934405016
- M moahmmed.9issa@gmail.com
- Ø github.com/Inferno-Team
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/mmi997

Education

2014-present
Aleppo University
Computer Engineering
4th academic year

Mohammed Mousa Alissa

Senior Android Developer

About Me

Android Developer with 8+ years of experience, using java, kotlin languages, MVVM pattern, Hilt (dependency Injection) and Graph Navigation. I can work part time remotly.

PS: All my Graduation projects are open source projects on my github account username: Inferno-Team

Work Experience

Women At Work | 21-07-2022 - Present Project Developer | My Day App

https://team-inferno-mobile-my-day-app.en.uptodown.com

Aleppo University | 2018-Present

Project Developer | Graduation Projects

- made more than 8 android applications and using pure php backend and java language
- made more than 7 android application using laravel backend and java and kotlin languages and 2 applications with Flutter framework

Expertise Skill

- Android Studio
- VS Code
- Adobe XD
- Back4app

Language Skill

- English
- Arabic

